{
    "subject": "resource/Nashville_(season_1)",
    "predicate": "property/episodenumber",
    "object": "19",
    "human_readable": "The episode number of Nashville (season 1) is 19.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8453434109687805,
            "question": "How many episodes are in season 1 of Nashville?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8328576683998108,
            "question": "How many episodes are there in Nashville's first season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7987550497055054,
            "question": "What is the episode number of the final episode of Nashville season 1?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7665263414382935,
            "question": "What television series has an episode count of 19 for its first season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7276971936225891,
            "question": "What is the final episode count for the first season of Nashville?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6490148305892944,
            "question": "Is there more than one season of Nashville?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5570551753044128,
            "question": "Is the number 19 a typical number of episodes for a television season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4329289197921753,
            "question": "Does Nashville have multiple seasons?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3857315480709076,
            "question": "What television show has a season with 19 episodes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3216676115989685,
            "question": "If the first episode is episode number 1, what is the last episode number in season 1?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The episode number of Nashville (season 1) is 19.",
            "html": "dbpedia_806_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What television show has a season with 19 episodes?",
            "html": "dbpedia_806_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Nashville have multiple seasons?",
            "html": "dbpedia_806_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is the number 19 a typical number of episodes for a television season?",
            "html": "dbpedia_806_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_806_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_806_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_806_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_806_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_806_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_806_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_806_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_806_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_806_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_806_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text mentions that the document describes information about \"Nashville season 3\". There's no information about \"Nashville (season 1)\".  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "The information in the documents does not support this triple. \n\nHere's why:\n- There are no season numbers mentioned for Season 1.\n- However, it talks about Nashville Season 3 which has 22 episodes.\n\nSo, the correct answer would be:\n\n{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about episodes in Nashville season 3 but do not mention anything related to the first season or its episode count. Specifically, it states that Nashville season 3 has 22 episodes, which contradicts the query stating the episode number of Nashville (season 1) is 19."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}